Register of the Center for the Study of Popular Culture Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- "The Honor and Duty of Fatherhood," 3rd annual fathers' conference, Anaheim, California, 1997 June 18-20. (Folder 74: 4)
  Brochure, clipping, letter, and rates of advertisement
- Prospective advertisers, 1996-1997. (Folder 74: 5)
  Brochures, newsletter, and statistical data relating to divorce rate
- Distribution, undated. (Folder 74: 6)
  List
- American Coalition for Fathers & Children, 1997. (Folder 74: 7)
  Invoice, letters, press release, and shipping record
- Advertising agreements for Fathers & Families, 1997. (Folder 74: 8)
- Divorce statistics, 1996-1997. (Folder 74: 9)
  Brochures, clippings, letters, and related materials
- Child support statistics, 1995-1996. (Folder 74: 10-11)
  Clippings and miscellany
- Resource page ideas, 1996. (Folder 74: 12)
- Miscellany, 1994-1997.
  Clippings, lists of "Fathers and Families" (database), letters, magazines, and press release. Includes mini sound cassettes--5 (packet labeled "Cloning"); 9 (packet labeled "Fathers and Families"); and 6 (packet labeled "Texas CEO")
- Alienation, 1996. (Box-folder 75: 1)
  Articles by others, clipping, letters. Includes letter to Sue Horton, Los Angeles Weekly, from Alan Rifkin regarding Sheila Kuehl's views on divorce and related issues
- SB145--Text, 1993 (Folder 75: 2)
- Good Dads Association, 1997. (Folder 75: 3)
  Letters and newsletter
- Correspondence--Fathers & Families, 1997 (Folder 75: 4)
- Dads Assisting Dads, Pinellas County, Florida, 1997. (Folder 75: 5)
  Invoice
- Diane Watson, 1984-1993. (Folder 75: 6)
- Horror stories relating to child abuse, 1995-1996. (Folder 75: 7)
  Includes invoice and related materials
- Jackie Speier, 1982-1994. (Folder 75: 8)
- California NOW, Inc.--Opponents of SB279, 1993. (Folder 75: 9)
  Includes a letter and testimony by Geraldine Jensen
- SB509, 1995. (Folder 75: 10)
  Text of the bill
- Ingrid and Haden Bower--Alimony, 1996. (Folder 75: 11)
- Fathers' rights bills, 1996. (Folder 75: 12)
  Information sheet
- Custody relocation, 1996. (Folder 75: 13)
  Clippings, articles by others, and related court papers
- Richard Halavais, 1996. (Folder 75: 14)
  Articles about child abuse and other family-related issues
- Lenore J. Weitzman, 1996. (Folder 75: 15)
- Sheila Kuehl, 1995-1996. (Folder 75: 16)
- AB180, 1995-1996. (Folder 75: 17)
  Clippings and articles relating to no-fault divorce laws, lowering child support in California, and related materials
- Court affiliated parent education, 1997. (Box-folder 76: 1)
  Clippings, invoice, newsletter, and miscellany
- Proposition 209--Lawsuits, 1996. (Folder 76: 2)
  Articles. Includes interviews on 4 mini sound cassettes
- Fathers & Families--, 1997 summer. (Folder 76: 3)
- AB999--Joint custody, 1995-1996. (Folder 76: 4)
  Bill texts, clippings, memoranda, and related materials
- Florida education, 1995-1996. (Folder 76: 5)
  Articles, clipping, and newsletter
- Coalition of Parent Support, Inc., 1995-1996. (Folder 76: 6)
- Picturing equality vigil, 1995-1996. (Folder 76: 7)
  Articles, bulletin, and related materials
- Submissims, 1995-1996. (Folder 76: 8)
  Articles relating to military spouses and miscellany
- Family articles, 1996 (Folder 76: 9)
- No-fault, 1996. (Folder 76: 10)
  Clipping and newsletter
- Insider's Report, 1996 (Box-folder 77: 1)
  on opposition to bilingual education
- Judicial nominations, 1996. (Folder 77: 2)
- Burbank airport, 1997. (Folder 77: 3)
  Articles and clipping
- Patrick J. Manshardt--Articles and clippings, 1996-1997 (Folder 77: 4)
- Miscellany, 1996-1997. (Folder 77: 5-6)
- Politically correct, 1996. (Folder 77: 7)
- Michael Savage, 1997. (Folder 77: 8)
- MSNBC, 1996. (Folder 77: 9)
  Article
- Public lands, 1995. (Folder 77: 10)
  Address and clippings
- Socialism, 1996. (Folder 77: 11)
  Articles by David Horowitz
- Torrance USD--, 1997. (Folder 77: 12)
- Hudson arbitration, 1994-1997. (Folder 77: 13)
- Robert Dole--Memorandum, 1995 (Box-folder 78: 1)
- First Amendment, 1993-1994. (Folder 78: 2)
- Bar reform, 1996. (Folder 78: 3)
- California Public Employee Relations (CPER), 1996. (Folder 78: 4)
- California Teachers' Association/National Education Association (CTA/NEA), 1994-1996. (Folder 78: 5)
  Articles and clippings
- Di Loreto case--Articles, 1997 (Folder 78: 6)
- ERISA/EEOC (Employee Retirement Income Security Act/Equal Employment Opportunity Commission), 1996. (Folder 78: 7)
- Steering committee biographies, 1997 (Folder 78: 8)
- Beverly Wilshire, undated. (Folder 78: 9)
- Rogers & Cowan, 1997. (Folder 78: 10)
- Billy Tauzin, 1997. (Folder 78: 11)
  Dinner invitations
- Wednesday Morning Club, 1996-1997. (Folder 78: 12-14)
- Michael Pack event, 1996. (Folder 78: 15)
  Biographies, financial records, guest registry, and related materials
- Frank Luntz dinner, 1996. (Folder 78: 16)
  Guest list, letters of invitation, and miscellany
- Xpedite fax cast instruction sheet, 1995 (Folder 78: 17)
- Spencer Abraham event, 1997. (Folder 78: 18)
  Contract, estimated charges, letters of invitation, list of people, and proposed menu
- Christopher Cox--Event, 1997. (Folder 78: 19)
  Biography, reminder letter, guest list, Xpedite instruction sheet
- Radical Son--David Horowitz's book event, 1997 February 20. (Folder 78: 20)
  Estimated charges, letter of invitation, guest list, and miscellany
- L.A. Farm, undated. (Folder 78: 21)
- 2 photographic contact sheets relating to the book-signing event, 1997 February 20
- Greater Talent Network, 1996. (Box-folder 79: 1)
  Biographies, brochure, and letter
- Buzz hour, 1996. (Folder 79: 2)
- Wednesday Morning Club registration forms and membership applications, undated (Folder 79: 3-5)
- "Images of Ourselves"--Chicago conference, 1996 February 24. (Folder 79: 6)
  Brochure and planning schedule
- Images conference
  - Miscellany, 1997 (Folder 79: 7)
  - Paid, 1997 (Folder 79: 8)
- Dinner--Alpha, 1999? (Folder 79: 9-13)
  Lists of guests, RSVPs, and table seating
- Sheraton room reservation, 1997 (Folder 79: 14)
- Confirmed participants, 1997 (Folder 79: 15)
- List of invitees, 1997 (Folder 79: 16)
- Disney room diagrams, 1997 (Folder 79: 17)
- Sheraton banquet, 1997 (Folder 79: 18)
- Sheraton--Maps and restaurants, 1997 (Folder 79: 19)
- Sheraton banquet program, 1997 (Folder 79: 20)
- VIP materials, 1997. (Folder 79: 21)
  Letters, information list, speakers list, and related materials
- Disney staff--Volunteer schedule, 1997 (Folder 79: 22)
- Travel arrangements, 1997 (Folder 79: 23)
- Disney
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Folder 79: 24)
  - Catering lunch, 1997 (Folder 79: 25)
  - Technical arrangements, 1997 (Folder 79: 26)
  - Audio-visual lists, 1997 (Folder 79: 27)
- "Images of Ourselves,", 1997. (Box-folder 80: 1)
- Disney list, undated (Folder 80: 2)
- Liberalism start date, 1996 January 29. (Box-folder 81: 1)
  Includes articles, description and potential benefit of the project, estimated cost, and miscellany
- Janice Brown--Swearing in of California high court, 1996 May 3. (Folder 81: 2)
- Gramsci's Marxism., 1998 October 29 (Folder 81: 3)
  Photocopies and a hate letter,
- Media watchdogs, 1997. (Folder 81: 4)
  Article and Counter Point newsletter
- Mein Hitler, by Eva Braun, undated (Folder 81: 5)
- Middle East, 1997. (Folder 81: 6)
- Million Man March--Farrakhan, 1995 October 13. (Folder 81: 7)
  Letters, remarks by Jesse Jackson, and related materials
- MSNBC--An inside look, 1996 October. (Folder 81: 8)
- Music, 1997. (Folder 81: 9)
  William J. Bennett's article
- Nation of Islam--Speech by Khalid Muhammad, San Francisco State University, 1997 May 21. (Folder 81: 10)
  Includes Final Call, 1997 July 1, and 1 compact sound cassette, "Prophet of Hate," 1993 November 29
- No Mercy: How Conservative Think Tanks and Foundations Changed America's Social Agenda--Letter, 1996 November 18 (Folder 81: 11)
  and photocopies of the cover and the contents page
- Wally Nunn--Articles on Septa, 1995, and on Green Again, 1995 (Folder 81: 12)
  Includes Privatization Watch, 1996 July
- Philadelphia Inquirer--Article, 1996 (Folder 81: 13)
- Philanthropy, 1997. (Box-folder 82: 1)
  Includes articles, journals, and road map
- "Rising Illegitimacy, Poverty, and Dependence in American Society"--Testimony, 1996 March 12 (Folder 82: 2)
  by Robert Rector before the United States Congress
- Politics, 1997. (Folder 82: 3)
- Power Rangers project, 1996. (Folder 82: 4)
- Predator/stalking--AB 1562, 1996. (Folder 82: 5)
- Race, 1997. (Folder 82: 6)
  Clippings. Includes Headway, 1997 July
- "The Real Pests Aren't in the Food," Wall Street Journal, 1996 September 18 (Folder 82: 7)
- Republican National Convention information, 1996 August 6 (Folder 82: 8)
- "Demonizing the Academy," adapted from "A Leg-up for Oliver North" by Richard Rorty, Harper's Magazine, 1995 January (Folder 82: 9)
- Donna Shalala--Article, Los Angeles Times, 1996 October 10 (Folder 82: 10)
- "Stage Veterans," article, L.A. Life, 1996 September 29 (Folder 82: 11)
- Articles, 1997. (Folder 82: 12)
  Quotes from left-wing stars
- Tailhook--Articles, 1993 October (Folder 82: 13)
- Television ratings, 1997. (Folder 82: 14)
  Articles, information packet, letters, and statements
- Television ratings per V-Chip legislation, 1996 December 20. (Folder 82: 15)
- Vietnam--Clippings, 1995 August 3 (Folder 82: 16)
- Memoranda to Comrade Dimitroff, 1938 January 19 (photocopy) and "Following the Evidence"--Article by John E. Haynes, 1996 May 4 (Folder 82: 17)
- Welfare, 1997. (Folder 82: 18)
- Women in the Military, 1997 May. (Folder 82: 19)
- 1960's--Article, 1998 January (Folder 82: 20)
- Brad O'Leary dinner, 2000 April 18. (Box-folder 83: 1)
- Bob Weingarten--Letters from Victor Zuniga, 2000 (Folder 83: 2)
- David Horowitz--Biography, undated (Folder 83: 3)
- Articles by David Horowitz, 1999-2000 (Folder 83: 4)
- Board members, undated (Folder 83: 5)
- Books sent out, 2000. (Folder 83: 6)
- Governor George Bush trip, 1999 April. (Folder 83: 7)
  Letters to Karl Rove, memoranda, list of invitees, personal information form, and record of money received
- Letters from
  - GQ Magazine, 1999 (Folder 83: 8)
  - Harvard University, 1999 November 1 (Folder 83: 9)
  - Howard University, 1999 February 25 (Folder 83: 10)
  - Hudson Institute, 1999 October 13 (Folder 83: 11)
  - Screen Actors Guild, undated (Folder 83: 12)
  - Copies of correspondence, 1998 (Folder 83: 13)
- Arizona, 1998. (Folder 83: 14)
  Letters and list of attendees for lunch hosted by the Goldwater Institute. Includes invitation for dessert at the home of Anna and Joseph Scherzer, 1998 April 14
- Correspondence, 1998. (Folder 83: 15)
  Includes agenda, articles, itinerary, memoranda, and schedule relating to David Horowitz's different trips
- CRAA list--Sally, undated (Folder 83: 16)
- Lincoln Club list--Sally, undated (Folder 83: 17)
- Time Magazine, 1999. (Folder 83: 18)
  Clipping, letters, memoranda, notes, and report
- The Nation--Letter to David Horowitz, 1999 November 5 (Folder 83: 19)
- Jerry Weller dinner, 1999 July 8. (Folder 83: 20)
  Includes thank you letters and call lists
- David Horowitz--Biography, undated
- Miscellany, 2000
- ABC love--Hollywood Concerned, undated. (Box-folder 84: 1)
- Black conservatives, 1997. (Folder 84: 2)
- Eldridge Cleaver, 1998. (Folder 84: 3)
- Geronimo Pratt, 1997. (Folder 84: 4)
  Articles by David Horowitz and clippings
- Marx/spies, 1997-1998. (Folder 84: 5)
- David Horowitz--Biography, undated (Folder 84: 6)
- Randal Brooks--Public relations, 1998. (Folder 84: 7)
  David Horowitz schedule
- Governor George W. Bush for President--Presidential Exploratory Committee, Inc., 1999. (Folder 84: 8)
  Fax cover sheets, forms to be completed by all contributors, list of names and telephone numbers, and memorandum
- Buzz--David Horowitz's letter to the editor about an article, "Broken Promise,", 1998 April 20. (Folder 84: 9)
  Includes photocopy of the article
- Citizens for Sound Economy, 1998. (Folder 84: 10)
- Century cable, 1997. (Folder 84: 11)
  Clippings, notes, and miscellany
- Congress, 1998. (Folder 84: 12)
  Clippings, fliers, handbook, letters from Peter King, Christopher Long, and Arlene Specter to David Horowitz, and press release
- Commonwealth Club of California, 1996. (Folder 84: 13)
  Itinerary, letters, and miscellany
- Press reports, 1997-1998. (Folder 84: 14)
  Banquet contract, invoice, biography of David Horowitz, clippings, printed matter, form letters, and materials relating to Larry Elders
- Background research, 1996-1997. (Folder 84: 15)
  Clippings about Larry Elders and miscellany
- Media information, 1997-1998. (Folder 84: 16)
  Clippings about Larry Elders
- David Horowitz's letters, 1997. (Folder 84: 17)
  Includes contract report and list of letters relating to Radical Son
- Jerry Falwell, 1999. (Folder 84: 18)
- Matt Drudge, 1998. (Folder 84: 19)
  Clippings and letters
- Free Enterprise Institute, 1998. (Folder 84: 20)
  Letter and memoranda about David Horowitz
- Harvard University, 1998. (Folder 84: 21)
  Letters to Alan Simpson and biography of Clark R. Bowers
- Heterodoxy writers, 1997. (Folder 84: 22)
  Article, clippings, form letter, and radio requests
- Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1998. (Folder 84: 23)
  Brochure, registration for conference participation, and related materials
- Individual Rights Foundation, 1995-1999. (Folder 84: 24)
  Brochure, clippings, press release, and miscellany
- Savage, Michael--KSFO radio, 1998. (Box-folder 85: 1)
- Femina--Independent Women's Forum, 1999. (Folder 85: 2)
  Newsletter
- American Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1998. (Folder 85: 3)
  Clippings, letters, lists, and miscellany
- Jewish Television Network (JTN). Thank you notes for participation in a show and related materials (Folder 85: 4)
- Israel--Articles, 1997. (Folder 85: 5)
  Includes lists, reports, and miscellany
- Sandy Stein, 1998. (Folder 85: 6)
  Clippings, flyers, issues of Response, and letters
- LA Weekly, 1999. (Folder 85: 7)
- Rush Limbaugh--Conversation with David Horowitz, undated. (Folder 85: 8)
  Includes The Limbaugh Letter, 1998 December
- Tawny Little, 1998. (Folder 85: 9)
  Letters and an announcement about a luncheon meeting featuring Dee Dee Myers and Arianna Huffington
- New Times, 1998. (Folder 85: 10)
  Clipping and letter from David Horowitz about an interview
- Op-Eds
  - Faxes at LA Times, 1998. (Folder 85: 11)
    Article by David Horowitz, announcement regarding Festival of Books, clippings, and letters
  - By David Horowitz, 1997-1998 (Folder 85: 12)
  - By others, 1997-1998 (Folder 85: 13)
  - Faxes, 1997-1998 (Folder 85: 14)
  - Newspaper responses, 1997-1998 (Folder 85: 15)
- Press, 1997. (Folder 85: 16)
  Article by David Horowitz, clippings, lists, and notes
- Articles and appearances by David Horowitz, 1995-1998 (Folder 85: 17-18)
- Radio/TV appearances, 1996-1997 (Folder 85: 19)
- Radio/TV appearances, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 86: 1)
- Texas
  - Greater Houston Pachyderm Club, 1997. (Folder 86: 2)
    Background information and letters to David Horowitz, who agreed to be a speaker at the club
  - The Rob McKinnon Show, 1997. (Folder 86: 3)
    Biography of the host, information about the show, and letters
- The Politics of Bad Faith: The Radical Assault on America's Future, by David Horowitz, 1998. (Folder 86: 4)
  Includes clippings, press release, and related materials
- First Things: A Journal of Religion and Politics, 1999. (Folder 86: 5)
  Photocopy of the cover page
- Jewish Exponent, 1999. (Folder 86: 6)
- Race Card, 1997. (Folder 86: 7)
  Biographical note about Peter Collier and David Horowitz, press release, reviews, and a check
- Trip to Arizona--Book signing and speaking engagements, 1998. (Folder 86: 8-9)
- Radical Son--Paperback promotion, 1998. (Folder 86: 10)
- Radical Son--Tour, 1998. (Folder 86: 11)
  Clippings, speaking engagement fact sheet, and miscellany
- Radical Son--Reviews, 1997-1998 (Folder 86: 12)
- The Politics of Bad Faith: The Radical Assault on America's Future--Publicity report, advertisements of David Horowitz's books, and clippings, 1998 (Folder 86: 13)
- Stranger than Fact, by Judith Schumann Weizner, 1997. (Folder 86: 14)
  Letters, book advertisements, and printed matter
- Radical Son--Outside publicity, 1997. (Folder 86: 15)
  Letters and press release
- American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1997. (Box-folder 87: 1)
- Affirmative action--Article, "Graglia Uproar: UT Law Professor Argues His Case,", 1997. (Folder 87: 2)
  Includes original article, related materials, and an issue of Allure
- AIDS--Clippings, 1996-1998 (Folder 87: 3)
- Yasser Arafat, 1997. (Folder 87: 4)
  Articles, clippings, and press release
- Stanley Aronowitz, 1997. (Folder 87: 5)
  Prologue--Last Good Job in America
- Bilingual education, 1997-1998. (Folder 87: 6)
  Articles and an issue of Reason
- Black Panthers, 1978-1998. (Folder 87: 7-9)
  Articles, clippings, letters, including one to the editor of Dissent, memoranda, tape recorded interview of Roger Lewis, and related materials
- Geronimo Pratt--Article and clippings (Folder 87: 10)
- Stokely Carmichael, 1998. (Folder 87: 11)
  Obituary
- Miscellany, 1997
- Proposition 209, 1996-1997. (Box-folder 88: 1)
  Clippings, letters to defendants and their counsel, research report, and related materials
- Charter schools, 1996. (Folder 88: 2)
- China--Press release, 1997 (Folder 88: 3)
- "Bill Clinton: A Case for Impeachment," article, Human Events, undated (Folder 88: 4)
- Civil rights, 1997. (Folder 88: 5)
  Article, Los Angeles Times
- CNN Crossfire--Transcript, 1996 (Folder 88: 6)
- Alexander Cockburn, undated. (Folder 88: 7)
- Compton Schools, 1996. (Folder 88: 8)
- Concerned Jews, 1996. (Folder 88: 9)
  Articles, letters, press release, and related materials
- Crime, 1996. (Folder 88: 10)
  Pacific Research Institute fact sheet and press release
- Steven G. Rhodes--Violent Crime Research project, 1996. (Folder 88: 11)
  Articles, clippings, and letters to David Horowitz
- Critical race theorists--Article, 1996 (Folder 88: 12)
- Article--Crown Heights, New York Times, 1997. (Folder 88: 13)
- Reviews of books by Angela Davis and others, 1989 (Folder 88: 14)
- Education, 1997. (Folder 88: 15)
- Environment, 1997. (Folder 88: 16)
  Articles and a report
- Philip Horowitz--FBI investigation, 1996. (Folder 88: 17)
  Relates to Unlimited Access and Freedom of Information Act
- Feminism--Article, 1997 (Folder 88: 18)
- "Foundations" and "Billion Dollar Brains" by David Horowitz, Ramparts, undated (Folder 88: 19)
- James Freedman--Dartmouth, 1997. (Folder 88: 20)
  Article, New York Times
- Gays and lesbians--Articles, 1998 (Folder 88: 21)
- Georgetown University Law Center--Brochures and final report, 1990-1995 (Folder 88: 22)
- Tom Hayden--Clipping, 1997 (Folder 88: 23)
- Charlton Heston, 1996. (Folder 88: 24)
- History--Article and letter to David Horowitz by Jon Louck, 1997 (Folder 88: 25)
- Hollywood--Blacklist memoirs, 1996-1997. (Folder 88: 26)
- AFL-CIO--Hollywood, 1996. (Folder 88: 27)
- Kelly Novak--Copy requested for non-UCLA users, 1998.
  Photocopies of articles
- Immigration--Alien Nation: Common Sense About America's Immigration Disaster, by Peter Brimelow, 1995 (Box-folder 89: 1)
- Indians--Form letter, 1998 (Folder 89: 2)
- Jews--Bernard Patrusky, 1996. (Folder 89: 3)
  Clippings and a letter to David Horowitz
- Elia Kazan, 1996-1997. (Folder 89: 4-5)
  Article, clippings, letters, list of Wednesday Morning Club members and Board of Directors
- John F. Kennedy Jr., 1997. (Folder 89: 6)
- Kosovo, 1999. (Folder 89: 7)
- Kennedy research--The sequel, 1996. (Folder 89: 8)
  Article and clippings
- Article--Vanity Fair, 1997 August (Folder 89: 9)
- Peter King--Farrakhan hot seat, 1996 July. (Folder 89: 10)
  Clippings and letter to David Horowitz
- "Killing of History: Why Relativism Is Wrong," by Roger Kimball, New Criterion, 1996 September (Folder 89: 11)
- Kwanza holiday, 1996 December. (Folder 89: 12)
- "Naked Greed," by Catherine Seipp, Buzz, 1997 May. (Folder 89: 13)
- David Levy--V-Chip issues, 1996 October 27. (Folder 89: 14)
- Fred Thompson event, 1996 August 17. (Box 90)
  Includes address, interviews of Pam Kelley, the Kennedys, Chris Lawford, and others, list of attendees, and related materials
- "Assess Your Source for the Best Responding Education Names,", 1997. (Box 91)
- Scrapbook--Letters etc., 1994-2001
- Fred Thompson event, 1996 August 17.
  Miscellany. Includes an issue of Los Angeles, 1996 March
- Miscellany, 2000-2001. (Box 92)
  Includes writings by David Horowitz and others, and materials relating to issues of media, politics, and race as expressed through the activities of the Center
- Benefactor Club meeting, 1995 May 31. (Box-folder 93: 1)
  Form letters, RSVP list, schedule, and other related materials
- Media lists, 1996 (Folder 93: 2)
- Education summit, Chicago, 1995 November 27. (Folder 93: 3)
  Includes banquet event order and fax cover sheets
- Chicago--Reception, 1996 April 24. (Folder 93: 4)
  Includes hotel information, letter seeking contribution, and menu
- The Weekend--New Year's gathering of conservatives, Miami, Florida, 1995 December 29-31. (Folder 93: 5)
  Includes list of attendees, menu, program, and 1 photographic print depicting David Horowitz and two unidentified individuals, undated
- San Francisco breakfast, 1994 November 24. (Folder 93: 6)
  Includes credit application, lists of invitees, notes, and thank you letters
- Tom Krantz lunch, 1995 February 25. (Folder 93: 7)
  Letters of invitation and thanks, and lists of attendees
- Board meeting, 1995 May 5. (Folder 93: 8)
  Menu and program
- David Jorgensen event, 1995 May 10. (Folder 93: 9)
  Letter of invitation and regrets, lists of guests, and RSVPs
- Wednesday Morning Club (WMC)
  - General information, 1995. (Folder 93: 10)
    Articles, clippings, list of events, and membership information
  - Fax lists. (Folder 93: 11)
    Includes partial list of attendees, 1995, and invitation to a private dinner, 1996 January 25
  - Invited speakers, 1994-1995 (Folder 93: 12)
  - Steering committee, 1995-1996. (Folder 93: 13)
    Includes agenda, biographies of Frank Price and Edgar J. Scherick, clippings, and letters
  - Jack Fields event, 1995 October 8. (Folder 93: 14)
    Includes invoice, letter, membership information, and related materials
  - Ben Wattenberg event, 1995 November 20. (Folder 93: 15)
    Includes event contract, invitation, menu, and related materials
  - Stephen Goldsmith event, 1996 January 24. (Folder 93: 16)
    Agenda, biography, invoice, letter of invitation, list of attendees, and press release
- Fred Thompson, 1996 January 30. (Box-folder 94: 1)
  Clippings, RSVP list, movie listings, list of attendees, letter of invitation, and related materials
- Jack Kemp, 1995 March 9. (Folder 94: 2)
  Invitation, itinerary, list of tables, and RSVP list
- Arlen Specter, 1995 April 12. (Folder 94: 3)
  Lists of invitations and RSVPs
- Bill Bennett, 1995 May 25. (Folder 94: 4)
  Invoice, list of guests, and miscellany
- Shutters on the Beach, Los Angeles, California, undated. (Folder 94: 5)
  Includes hotel policies and general information
- Wyndham Hotels and Resorts, West Hollywood, California, undated. (Folder 94: 6)
  Includes direction, location, and miscellany
- University of California Catering, Los Angeles, California, undated. (Folder 94: 7)
  General information
- Four Seasons Hotel, Los Angeles, California--General information, undated (Folder 94: 8)
- Hotel Inter-Continental, Los Angeles, California. Letters and miscellany, undated (Folder 94: 9)
- Loews: Santa Monica Beach Hotel, Los Angeles, California. Floor map, letter of thanks from the hotel, and menu, 1995 (Folder 94: 10)
- Radisson Bel-Air Summit Hotel, Los Angeles, California, undated. (Folder 94: 11)
  Menu
- Center clips, 1992-1996 (Folder 94: 12)
- Beverly Hilton, Beverly Hills, California, 1995. (Folder 94: 13)